All right, I'll say good day. As you can
plainly see by the shirt the channel is
wearing, the title of this transmission
is
2027, the year everything
changes. We have talked about the idea
that open contact is about to happen is
imminent within two years.
They will be officially introduced to
your
society at first most likely hybrids,
plleadenss and then others.
So this probably relates to the idea of
this question which is if the formula
works perfectly then why are there so
many starving artists? Why is the
starving artist even a thing?
This question assumes that all artists
are actually acting on their
passions. The idea also is you have to
look at what the life plan is of these
people. Sometimes it may include many
challenges that don't allow them to
experience the benefits of following
their passion right away because that
may serve other purposes for them to
learn other kinds of lessons or that the
people around them that are in relation
with them are learning lessons from
their experience as well.
So it is kind of an assumption on the
part of this questioner that anyone who
calls themsself an artist is actually
automatically acting on their passion
when they may not be. And this person is
ignoring the fact that different people
choose different life paths for
different reasons. And even though they
may express the idea of their life path
artistically, doesn't necessarily mean
that that is a logical conclusion for
them to say that they will experience
that in a positive way depending upon
why they chose to experience that. So
you have to look at the reasons for the
life path and the lessons that that
person is learning.
And perhaps that integrates with this
question which is when you say we are
given what we need by life instead of
what we want. Does this mean that a
person shouldn't make any efforts
towards manifesting their desires and
wants? Because life will give them what
it thinks is right. Sometimes I feel
scared about this unknown factor that
life may throw at us. How do we deal
with this fear? Well, first you have to
have a deeper understanding of the
formula that we're giving you because
then you would know that anything that
comes to you is going to benefit you if
you stay in a positive state and
approach the challenge with
curiosity. The idea also is to
understand
that what you need will fulfill you
although sometimes what you want won't.
So you have to learn the difference
between your negative ego assumptions
and the idea of what it is your soul
knows is actually going to benefit you.
If you use it in that positive way, if
you stay in that state of neutrality,
curiosity and openness, you will get
what you need and you will be fulfilled.
You have to have a deeper understanding,
a more precise understanding of how the
formula works.
[Music]